Hello everyone welcome on Mi Tube channel 021
in this video we are going to do detailed technical analysis of Mankind Pharma company,
as you can see we recently got to see the IPO of this company,
after that we are continuously seeing a great boom
in the stock and
today also a great boom was seen in this stock,
now this stock
can see profit booking from here
because RSS has gone up to 80, last
time also profit booking was seen in this stock after reaching 80, if we look at the
weekly
time frame then at the
time this stock is hyper right now on the weekly time frame,
after breaking the level of ₹2000
we can see this stock running faster
and this stock will
also be seen till 202100 but
after this toprose now your stop loss will be
here at 1723 which is the low of this candle, if we
talk about monthly time frame then
your stop loss on monthly time frame will be
here at 1657  If we talk about the target, it will be of Rs.
and it can rise further
if it properly breaks the level of ₹1900,
then comment on which stock the next video should be
and did you
get this IPL, please tell us by commenting,
thank you friends.